# Konika Das

# **Email Outreach Specialist**

Email: konikadas@outlook.com | Phone: +91 9908604942

Location: Visakhapatnam, India

## **Objective:**

To leverage my Hubspot certification and two years of experience in email marketing as an Email Outreach Specialist at TLG where I can utilize my skills to develop and implement effective email campaigns that engage and convert target audiences.

# **Professional Experience:**

#### **Web Content Writer**

Outreach Chimp, Virtual (2022)

• Produced SEO-friendly web content for a coupon website.

#### **Career Detour**

System Engineer Trainee
Infosys Limited, Virtual (2022-2023)

## **Program Manager**

Scientific Federation, Visakhapatnam (2020-2022)

- Developed and executed email campaigns, increasing audience engagement.
- Wrote and reviewed new cold outreach templates for my team.
- Managed inboxes and regularly maintained email and social media conversations with prospects.
- Handled large volumes of emails and email lists spanning thousands.
- Updated website content for relevance in clear and concise English.
- Crafted persuasive promotional material for social media platforms.
- Proofread all email and website content created by the team.

## **Marketing Intern**

Book Hub, Virtual (2018)

#### **Campus Ambassador**

Internshala, Virtual (2017)

#### **Education:**

Bachelor of Technology in Electronics and Communication Welfare Institute of Science, Technology, And Management (Andhra University) 2016 - 2020 Senior Secondary (XII), Science

Narayana Junior College (SSC board)

Year of completion: 2016

Secondary (X)

Annamma Secondary School (ICSE board)

Year of completion: 2014

#### **Skills:**

- Content Writing
- Creative Writing
- English Proficiency (Written & Spoken)
- Proofreading and Editing
- Email Marketing
- Microsoft Office Suite
- Audience Segmentation
- A/B Testing
- Mailchimp
- Effective Communication
- Social Media Marketing
- Digital Marketing

# **Accomplishments:**

- Enhanced user engagement through compelling email marketing campaigns.
- Received positive feedback for consistently error-free materials.
- Hosted successful webinars with participants from diverse backgrounds.
- Earned appraisals twice for my work at Scientific Federation.

### **Certifications:**

**Hubspot Academy: Email Marketing** 

### Languages:

Hindi, English, Telugu